const javaModule1Questions = [
    {
        question: "_____ consists of seperate prgrams for developing and testing Java programs, each of which is invoked from a command line",
        studyGuideInformation: "A JDK is a software development kit used by Java developers. It consists of separate programs for developing and testing Java programs, each of which is invoked from a command line.",
        correctAnswer: "JDK",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "JRE", 
            "JVM", 
            "JRE and JVM"
        ]
    },
   
    {
        question: "Java was developed by _____",
        studyGuideInformation: "Java was developed by Sun Microsystems.",
        correctAnswer: "Sun Microsystems",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Oracle", 
            "IBM", 
            "Microsoft"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which JDK command is correct to run a Java application in ByteCode.class",
        studyGuideInformation: "The correct command to run a Java application in ByteCode.class is java ByteCode.",
        correctAnswer: "java ByteCode",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "javac ByteCode", 
            "java ByteCode.class", 
            "javac ByteCode.class"
        ]
    },
    { 
        question: "The JDK command to compile a class in the file Test.java is ________.",
        studyGuideInformation: "The JDK command to compile a class in the file Test.java is javac Test.java.",
        correctAnswer: "javac Test.java",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "javac Test", 
            "java Test.java", 
            "java Test"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following lines are not a Java comment?",
        studyGuideInformation: "The correct answer is //This is a comment.",
        correctAnswer: "//This is a comment.",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "/This is a comment./", 
            "/*This is a comment.", 
            "This is a comment."
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "________ contains predefined classes and interfaces for developing Java programs.",
        studyGuideInformation: "The Java API contains predefined classes and interfaces for developing Java programs.",
        correctAnswer: "Java API",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "JDK", 
            "JRE", 
            "JVM"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The main method header is written as ________.",
        studyGuideInformation: "The main method header is written as public static void main(String[] args).",
        correctAnswer: "public static void main(String[] args)",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "public static void main(String args)", 
            "public void main(String[] args)", 
            "public void main(String args)"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "________ provides an integrated development environment (IDE) for rapidly developing Java programs. Editing, compiling, building, debugging, and online help are integrated in one graphical user interface.",
        studyGuideInformation: "NetBeans provides an integrated development environment (IDE) for rapidly developing Java programs. Editing, compiling, building, debugging, and online help are integrated in one graphical user interface.",
        correctAnswer: "Java IDE",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Notepad", 
            "TXT Document", 
            "Insomnia"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Java is ______",
        studyGuideInformation: "A platform-neutral language is a programming language that can run on any type of computer.",
        correctAnswer: "Architecture Neutral",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Platform Negative", 
            "Architecture-Positive", 
            "Platform Neutral"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following statements is correct to display Welcome to Java on the console?",
        studyGuideInformation: "The correct statement to display Welcome to Java on the console is System.out.println(\"Welcome to Java\");.",
        correctAnswer: "System.out.println(\"Welcome to Java\");",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "System.out.print(\'Welcome to Java\");", 
            "System.println(\"Welcome to Java\");", 
            "System.out.println(\"Welcome to Java\")"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "________ is interpreted.",
        studyGuideInformation: "Java is interpreted.",
        correctAnswer: "Java",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "C++", 
            "C", 
            "Assembly"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        question: "Which of the following are the reserved words?",
        studyGuideInformation: "The correct answer is int.",
        correctAnswer: "Class, int, void",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "That, With, Never",
            "When, it, is",
            "Structure, Class, Void"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "In order to compile a program with a class called Yellow, the source code should be stored in ",
        studyGuideInformation: "In order to compile a program with a class called Yellow, the source code should be stored in a file called Yellow.java.",
        correctAnswer: "A file called Yellow.java",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "A file called Yellow", 
            "A file called Yellow.class", 
            "A file called Yellow.java.class"
        ]
    }
];

const basicComputerScienceQuestions = [
    {
        question: "windows is an _____ _______",
        studyGuideInformation: "Windows is an operating system.",
        correctAnswer: "Operating System",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "IDE", 
            "JDK", 
            "Development Environment"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Why do computers use zeros and ones?",
        studyGuideInformation: "Computers use zeros and ones because they are binary systems.",
        correctAnswer: "because digital  devices have two stable states and it is natural to use one state for 0 and the other for 1.",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "because it is easier to use zeros and ones", 
            "because it is easier to use zeros and ones", 
            "because it is easier to use zeros and ones"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "One byte has ______ bits.",
        studyGuideInformation: "One byte has 8 bits.",
        correctAnswer: "8",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "16", 
            "4", 
            "2"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Computer can execute the code in ______",
        studyGuideInformation: "Computer can execute the code in ByteCode.class.",
        correctAnswer: "Machine code",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "high language code", 
            "Source code", 
            "Assembly code"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "_______ are instructions to the computer.",
        studyGuideInformation: "Programs are instructions to the computer.",
        correctAnswer: "Programs",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "Hardware", 
            "Inputs", 
            "Development Environments"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        question: "Java compiler translates Java source code into ________ another high-level language code ",
        studyGuideInformation: "Java compiler translates Java source code into byte code.",
        correctAnswer: "byte code",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "machine code", 
            "assembly code", 
            "binary code"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The speed of the CPU may be measured in ________.",
        studyGuideInformation: "The speed of the CPU may be measured in gigahertz.",
        correctAnswer: "gigahertz",
        incorrectAnswers: [
            "bytes", 
            "megaBytes", 
            "wattz"
        ]
    },
];